ABDERRAHIM NABAOUI

UNITY GAME DEVELOPER

@ nabaoui.abderrahim@gmail.com +212637852855

Agadir, Morocco



https://www.gamox.ma/portfolio

 Unity game programmer with over 8 years of experience in programming and problem solving, 5 years in web/mobile development, and 3 years in the gaming field. In 2020 I launched my start-up Gamox (Gamox.ma) to get in touch with other hyper-casual studios. and recently I worked with 9tales (9tales.io) to release their NFT demo card game.

Experience

Unity Game Developer

 www.9tales.io **9tales**

- Create 9tales demo NFT card game.
- Transform 100% of design specification into functional games.
- Implement some of the game 3D models and VFX.
- Communicate with other 3 team members.

Gamox CEO

■ Gamox

2020 - 2022

2021 - 2022

- Led my startup to create 4 hyper-casual mobile games in Unity 3D.
- Collaboration with Moonee studio publisher on 3 hyper-casual games, (Brain Master 3D, Stack Crowds Running 3D, Stack Crowds Running 3D)

1337 School Projects

1337

2016 - 2018

- Make a small Ray tracing engine in C language, supporting mirror effect, transparency and texture in 3D space.
- Recreate Shadowmatic full game from scratch in unity 3D.

Project Manager

Fikralabs # www.fikralabs.com # 2016 - Present

- Developed the 1st platform web to announce used cars for sell.
- Designed 3 websites: Fikralabs, Hotel Targante, If-company.
- Developed Lqliaa Municipality website.

Education

Information Technology Architect (Computer Graphic)

1337 Coding School

2018 - 2022

 Studying computer graphic, and make a small ray tracing rendering engine with C language, and small other games with unity.

Associate Degree in web Development and Multimedia (Web Development)

EWA School Agadir

2013 - 2015

• Learning the basics of algorithms and problem solving, make websites with HTML/CSS and backend with php.

Two Years in Faculty Option Physics (Physics)

Science Faculty IBN ZOHR (FSA)

2011 - 2013

Two Years in Faculty Option Physics.

Skills

Unity 3D • C#

HTML/CSS

Git

Blender

Adobe Photoshop

Achievement

Speaker @ DevFest Agadir

GDG Agadir

Flutter Workshop.

Participation @ Google for MENA Summit

Google

12/2019 Dubai

 Summit for all Google Developers Leaders organised 100% by Google in Dubai.

Participation @ AiHackTunisia

Google and InstaDeep

• 1st Intelligence Artificielle Hackathon organised by Google and InstaDeep in Tunisia.

1337 Game Jam

1337

1 02/2019 Khouribga

• Game about Women's day theme.

Portfolio

- www.github.com/azertfx
- www.behance.net/azertfx
- m www.linkedin.com/in/abderrahimnabaoui

Languages

Arabic Native English Intermediate French Intermediate